Guide to the David Tibet Current 93 archive, 1960s-circa 2013.
Tibet, David Current 93 archive
- Series VI. Audio/Visual Material
  - Subseries VI d. Records (Other)
    - Hirsche Nicht Aufs Sofa, SR-10079 (Box 14)
    - Howth Castle, SR-10080 (Box 18)
      Rust of Keys
    - Howth Castle, SR-10081 (Box 19)
      Good Morning Nobody
    - Hurley, Mike, SR-10082 (Box 19)
      First Songs
    - Hush Arbors (Box 14)
      [Missing Vinyl]
    - Incredible, SR-10083 (Box 14)
      Kaleidoscope/Bernice
    - Ignis Fatuus, SR-10084-10085 (Box 19)
      White Willow
    - Jan Dukes de Grey, SR-10086 (Box 19)
      Sorcerers
    - Jex Thoth, SR-10087 (Box 19)
      Witness
    - The Joy of Nature, SR-10088 (Box 14)
      The Shepherd's Tea at 7
    - Kloster, SR-10089 (Box 19)
      Do Not be Afraid
    - Koning's Blauw, SR-10090 (Box 14)
      Light Inside my Head/Time Machine
    - Konori, SR-10091 (Box 14)
      SP.
    - Kvaedamannafelagid, SR-10326 (Box 23)
      100 Islensk Kvaedalog
    - L (2), SR-10092 (Box 14)
      Holy Letter
    - Lemon Kittens, SR-10093 (Box 19)
      Cake Beast
    - Lemon Kittens, SR-10094 (Box 19)
      The Big Dentist
    - Lemon Kittens, SR-10095 (Box 19)
      We Buy a Hammer for Daddy
    - Lemon Kittens, SR-10096 (Box 14)
      Spoonfed and Writhing
    - Lichens, SR-10097 (Box 19)
      The Pyschic Nature of Reing
    - Little Feat, SR-10098 (Box 19)
      Down on the Farm
    - Little Feat, SR-10099 (Box 19)
      Let it Roll
    - Little Feat, SR-10100-10101 (Box 19)
      Chinese Bejeezus
    - Little Feat, SR-10102-10103 (Box 19)
      Waiting for Columbus
    - Little Feat, SR-10104 (Box 19)
      Electrif Lycanthrope
    - Little Feat, SR-10105 (Box 19)
      Wheeling and Dealing
    - Little Feat, SR-10106 (Box 19)
      Beak Positive
    - Little Feat, SR-10107 (Box 19)
      The Last Record Album
    - Little Feat, SR-10108 (Box 19)
      Rampant Syncopatio
    - Martin, Andreas, SR-10109 (Box 19)
      Doppelpunk vor Ort
    - Martin, Andreas; Basinski, William; Heemann, Christoph, SR-10110-10111 (Box 14)
    - Martin, Robert, SR-10112 (Box 19)
      Long Goodbye
    - Mark Fry, SR-10113 (Box 14)
    - Masayoshi, Urabe; Chie, Mukai, SR-10114 (Box 19)
      Dual Anarchism
    - Masstishaddhu, SR-10115 (Box 19)
      Shekina
    - Maya, SR-10116 (Box 19)
      Power
    - Maya, SR-10117 (Box 19)
      Helium
    - Mayhem, SR-10118 (Box 19)
      Live in Marseille 2000
    - Mayhem, SR-10119 (Box 19)
      Ordo Ad Chao
    - Mayhem, SR-10120-10124 (Box 19)
      The Studio Experience
    - McCord, Kathy, SR-10125 (Box 19)
      Kathy McCord
    - McDonald, Shelagh, SR-10126 (Box 19)
      Shelagh McDonald Album
    - McDonald, Shelagh, SR-10127 (Box 19)
      Star Gazer
    - McDowall, Rose, SR-10128 (Box 19)
      Don't Fear the Reaper
    - McDowall, Rose, SR-10129 (Box 14)
    - Melnyk, Lubomyr, SR-10130 (Box 19)
      KMH
    - Menace Ruine, SR-10131 (Box 19)
      The Die is Cast
    - Merle Evans and his Circus Band, SR-10132 (Box 20)
      Circus in Town!
    - Metzger, Paul, SR-10133 (Box 20)
      Four Improvisations on Modified Banjo and Guitar
    - Metzger, Paul, SR-10134 (Box 20)
      Solo Acoustic LP
    - Migrantes, SR-10135 (Box 20)
      Moon Journals
    - Mimir, SR-10136 (Box 20)
      Mimyriad
    - Mimir, SR-10137 (Box 20)
      Mimir
    - Mirror, SR-10138 (Box 20)
      Nights
    - Mirror, SR-10139 (Box 20)
      Still Valley
    - Mirror, SR-10140 (Box 20)
      Die Spiegelmanufaktur
    - Mirror, SR-10141 (Box 20)
      Islands
    - Mirror, SR-10142 (Box 20)
      I Paint for the Color of Love
    - Mirror, SR-10143 (Box 20)
      Front Row Centre
    - Mirror, SR-10144 (Box 20)
      Ringstones
    - Mirror, SR-10145 (Box 20)
      Nightwalkers
    - Mirror, SR-10146 (Box 20)
      Visiting Star
    - Mirror, SR-10147 (Box 20)
      Under the Sun
    - Mirror, SR-10148 (Box 14)
    - Mirror, SR-10149 (Box 14)
      Pedestrian Nocturne
    - Moore, Steven, SR-10150 (Box 20)
      The Henge
    - Moore, Thurston, SR-10151-10152 (Box 20)
      Demolished Thoughts
    - A Mouse Orchestra, SR-10153-10154 (Box 14)
      A Lump in Your Throat (two copies)
    - Musique Concret, SR-10155 (Box 20)
      Bringing Up Baby
    - Neon Knights; Magick Lantern Cycle, SR-10156 (Box 20)
      Al-Kitab Alf Laylah Wa Laylah Vol. 1
    - Neon Pearl, SR-10157 (Box 20)
      1967 Recordings
    - New Blockaders, SR-10158 (Box 20)
      The Final Recordings
    - Nihilist Spasm Band, SR-10159 (Box 20)
      1x-x=x
    - Noel Von Harmonson; Chasny, SR-10160 (Box 20)
      Plays the Book of Revelation
    - Nomi Klaus, SR-10161 (Box 14)
      Total Eclipse/Falling in Love
    - O'Rourke, Jim, SR-10162 (Box 20)
      Two Organs
    - O'Rourke, Jim, SR-10163 (Box 20)
      Scend
    - O'Sullivan, Gilbert, SR-10164 (Box 20)
      Greatest Hits
    - O'Sullivan, Gilbert, SR-10165 (Box 20)
      Back to Front
    - O'Sullivan, Gilbert, SR-10166 (Box 20)
      I'm a Writer, Not a Fighter
    - Oldfield, Harry, SR-10167 (Box 20)
      Crystal
    - Oldham, Will, SR-10168 (Box 21)
      We All, Us Three, Will Ride
    - Operating Theatre, SR-10170 (Box 20)
    - Ora, SR-10171 (Box 20)
      Isle
    - Ora, SR-10172 (Box 20)
      Aureum
    - Ora, SR-10173-10174 (Box 20)
      Amalgam
    - Organum, SR-10175 (Box 20)
      Submission
    - Ornamental, SR-10176 (Box 20)
      No Pain
    - Ornamental, SR-10177 (Box 21)
      Crystal Nights
    - Ornamental, SR-10178 (Box 22)
    - Palestine, Charlemagne, SR-10179 (Box 22)
      Strumming Music
    - Palestine, Charlemagne, SR-10180-10181 (Box 22)
      Holy 1/Holy 2/Holy 1+2
    - Pantaleimon, SR-10182 (Box 22)
      Trees Hold Time
    - Pantaleimon, SR-10183 (Box 21)
      Under the Water
    - Pataphonie, SR-10184 (Box 22)
      Pataphonie
    - Perhacs, Linda, SR-10185 (Box 22)
      Parallelograms
    - Pillars and Tongues, SR-10186 (Box 22)
      Lay of Pilgrim Park
    - Plague Lounge, SR-10187 (Box 22)
      The Wicker Image
    - Genesis Breyer P-orridge and Thee Early Worm, SR-10188 (Box 22)
      Early Worm
    - Public Foot the Roman, SR-10189 (Box 22)
      Public Foot the Roman
    - Quad, SR-10190 (Box 22)
      Inner Groove/Outer Groove
    - Quad, SR-10191 (Box 22)
      Temple Projection/Revisitation Mantra
    - Rice, Boyd, SR-10192 (Box 22)
    - Roberts, John; Barrand, Tony, SR-10193 (Box 22)
      Dark Ships in the Forest: Ballads of the Supernatural
    - Ronson, Mick, SR-10194 (Box 22)
      Play Don't Worry
    - Rose, Jack, SR-10195 (Box 22)
      Kensington Blues
    - Roundtree, Tommy, SR-10196 (Box 22)
      Jungle Blood
    - Ryan, Collie, SR-10197 (Box 22)
      The Hour is Now
    - Schwarze, Stupor, SR-10198 (Box 21)
      Stampe in Memoriam
    - Scott, Raymond, SR-10199 (Box 21)
    - Servile Sect, SR-10200 (Box 22)
      Stratoshperic Passenger
    - Shearwater, SR-10202 (Box 22)
      Rook
    - Shock Headed Peters, SR-10203 (Box 22)
      Life Extinguisher
    - Shock Headed Peters, SR-10204 (Box 22)
      The Kissing of Gods
    - Shock Headed Peters, SR-10205 (Box 22)
      I, Bloodbrother Be
    - Shock Headed Peters, SR-10206 (Box 22)
      Fear Engine
    - Shock Headed Peters, SR-10207 (Box 22)
      Not Born Beautiful
    - Shrinebuilder, SR-10208-10209 (Box 22)
      Shrinebuilder
    - The Amazing Mrs. Shufflewick, SR-10210 (Box 22)
      Live! At the New Black Cap
    - Silmaril, SR-10211 (Box 22)
      The Voyage of Icarus
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10212 (Box 22)
      Nightly Trembling
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10213-10214 (Box 21)
      Somewhere Between her Shoulder and God
    - Six Organs of Admittance; Colossal Yes, SR-10215 (Box 21)
      All the be/The Honeycreeper Smiles
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10216 (Box 21)
      It Was Written/On Distance
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10217 (Box 22)
      Invitation to the SR for Supper
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10218-10220 (Box 22)
      RTZ
    - Six Organs of Admittance; Charalambides, SR-10221 (Box 22)
      Songs from the Entoptic Garden Volume Two
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10222 (Box 22)
      For Octavio Paz
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10223 (Box 22)
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10224 (Box 22)
      Shelter from the Ash
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10225 (Box 22)
      Dark Noontide
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10226 (Box 22)
      Asleep on the Floodplain
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10227 (Box 24)
      Days of Blood
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10228 (Box 24)
      School of the Flower
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10229 (Box 24)
      Compathia
    - Six Organs of Admittance, SR-10230 (Box 24)
      Luminous Night
    - Skitliv, SR-10231 (Box 24)
      Skandinavisk Misantropi
    - Sleep, SR-10232 (Box 24)
      Sleep's Holy Mountain
    - Sleep, SR-10233 (Box 24)
      Volume One
    - Sleep, SR-10234 (Box 24)
      Dopesmoker
    - Sleep, SR-10235-10236 (Box 21)
      Volume Two (two copies)
    - Son of Earth; Double Leopards, SR-10237 (Box 24)
      Son of Earth/Double Leopards
    - Sorrow, SR-10238 (Box 21)
      Let There Be Thorns
    - Spell, SR-10239 (Box 24)
      Seasons in the Sun
    - Spires that in the Sunset Rise, SR-10240 (Box 24)
      Spires that in the Sunset Rise
    - Steals, Armand Schaubroeck, SR-10241-10242 (Box 24)
      A Lot of People Would Like to See Armand Schaubroeck…DEAD
    - Steals, Armand Schaubroeck, SR-10243 (Box 24)
      Ratfucker
    - Steals, Armand Schaubroeck, SR-10244-10245 (Box 24)
      Live at the Holiday Inn
    - Steals, Armand Schaubroeck, SR-10246 (Box 24)
      Shakin' Shakin'
    - Stoecklein, Val, SR-10247 (Box 24)
      Grey Life
    - Stone Axe, SR-10248 (Box 21)
      Stone Axe
    - Stoughton, David, SR-10249 (Box 24)
      Transformer
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10250 (Box 21)
      I Can Feel
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10251 (Box 21)
      Let Her Go
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10252-10253 (Box 21)
      Since Yesterday (two copies)
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10254-10255 (Box 21)
      Trees and Flowers/Go Away (two copies)
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10256 (Box 24)
      Trees and Flowers/Go Away
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10257 (Box 24)
      Jolene
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10258 (Box 24)
      Who Knows What Love Is?
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10259 (Box 24)
    - Strawberry Switchblade, SR-10260 (Box 24)
      The 12" Album
    - M.S. Subbulakshmi, SR-10261 (Box 24)
      Sri Venkateswara Pancharatna Mala
    - Sunn O))), SR-10262 (Box 24)
      Agharthi Live
    - Sunn O))); Earth 2, SR-10263 (Box 24)
      Coma Mirror
    - Sveinbjorn Beinteinsson Kvedur, SR-10264 (Box 24)
      Eddukvadi
    - Terry, SR-10265 (Box 24)
      Rojvi
    - These New Puritans, SR-10266 (Box 24)
      Swords of Trutch
    - These New Puritans, SR-10267 (Box 24)
      Hidden Remixes
    - These New Puritans, SR-10268 (Box 24)
    - Thighpaulsandra, SR-10269 (Box 24)
      Chamber Music
    - Thighpaulsandra, SR-10270 (Box 21)
      The Michael Publicity Window EP
    - Thirsty Moon, SR-10271 (Box 24)
      You'll Never Come Back
    - Thread, SR-10272-10274 (Box 21)
      Brainwashed (three copies)
    - Tietchens, Asmus, SR-10275 (Box 24)
      Formen Letzter Hausmusik
    - Tir Na Nog, SR-10276 (Box 24)
      Tir Na Nog
    - Tormentor, SR-10277 (Box 24)
      The Seventh Day of Doom
    - Toth, James Jackson, SR-10278-10279 (Box 24)
      Waiting in Vain
    - Towhshend, Pete, SR-10280 (Box 24)
      Chinese Eyes
    - Tucker, Mark, SR-10282 (Box 23)
      In the Sack
    - Two Daughters, SR-10283 (Box 23)
      Kiss the Girl/Gloria
    - Ultra, SR-10284 (Box 23)
      Youthful Pleasures
    - The Underneath, SR-10285 (Box 23)
      Lunatic Dawn of the Dismantler
    - The Underneath, SR-10286 (Box 23)
      The Imp of the Perverse
    - Various Artists, SR-10287-10289 (Box 23)
      By the Fruits You Shall Know the Roots
    - Various Artists, SR-10290 (Box 23)
      Tibetan Songs of Gods and Demons
    - Various Artists, SR-10291-10292 (Box 23)
      Matter Dominates Spirit
    - Various Artists, SR-10293 (Box 23)
      Sacred Bones Records
    - Various Artists, SR-10294 (Box 23)
      Sound Cosmodel
    - Various Artists, SR-10295-10296 (Box 23)
      The Tale of Ale
    - Various Artists, SR-10297 (Box 21)
      Prolemaic Terrascope
    - Various Artists, SR-10298 (Box 21)
      The Tectonic Ptolecope
    - VK 88, SR-10299 (Box 23)
      Alles Uber Atemtechnik
    - The Venerable Chimed Rig Dzin Lama Rinpoche, SR-10300 (Box 23)
      The Venerable Chimed Rig Dzin Lama Rinpoche
    - Vitet, Bernard; La Guepe, SR-10301 (Box 23)
      Futura Son 05
    - The Volares, SR-10302 (Box 23)
      The Night we Taught Ourselves to Sing
    - Wall of Voodoo, SR-10303 (Box 23)
      Happy Planet
    - Wand, SR-10304 (Box 23)
      Born Bad
    - Waters, Patty, SR-10305 (Box 23)
      College Tour
    - Waters, Patty, SR-10306 (Box 23)
      Patty Waters Sings
    - White Magic, SR-10307 (Box 23)
      Through the Sun Door
    - White Willow, SR-10308 (Box 23)
      Terminal Twilight
    - Wolves in the Throne Room, SR-10309 (Box 23)
      Live at Roadburn
    - Wolfli, Adolf, SR-10310 (Box 23)
      Necropolis, Amphibians and Reptiles
    - Woodward, Edward, SR-10311 (Box 23)
      It Had to be You
    - Xasthur, SR-10312-10313 (Box 23)
      Nocturnal Poisoning
    - Xhol Caravan; Motherfuckers Live, SR-10314-10315 (Box 23)
      Hot Buttered Xhol
    - Yazijian, Ed, SR-10316 (Box 23)
      Six Ways to Avoid the Evil Eye
    - Yonkers, Michael; Woehrle, Jim, SR-10317 (Box 23)
      Borders of My Mind
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10318 (Box 23)
      It's Only Yonkers
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10319 (Box 23)
      Grimwood
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10320 (Box 23)
      Yonkers, Michael
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10321 (Box 23)
      Goodby Sunball
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10322 (Box 23)
      Thy Will Be Done
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10323 (Box 23)
      Microminiature Love
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10324 (Box 21)
    - Yonkers, Michael, SR-10325 (Box 21)
      The Flowers Bloom